Preliminary Guide to the Robert H. Woody papers, 1927-1985
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List:
  - Historical letters, typewritten copies (Folder 351, Box 4)
  - Printed materials on publishing historical documents (Folder 352, Box 4)
  - Hart, Liddell, The Psychology of a Commander, and General R.E. Lee: His Latest Biography (Folder 353, Box 4)
  - Foreign military writers and Civil War (Folder 354, Box 4)
  - Southern literacy (Folder 355, Box 4)
  - Sevier, J. and Telfair, 1786, letter, typewritten copy (Folder 356, Box 4)
  - Reel 1 (Box 5)
    - Gardens Parade and Faculty Club Picnic, 1949 (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (200 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 2 (Box 5)
    - Catalochee reunion, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (175 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 3 (Box 5)
    - Mountains, undated (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (175 ft) (Box 5)
  - Reel 4 (Box 5)
    - History Department, Duke University, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (200 ft) (Box 5)
  - Reel 5 (Box 5)
    - History Department II, undated (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (25 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 6 (Box 5)
    - Southern Historical Association, 1949 (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col (200 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 7 (Box 5)
    - July 13-14, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (25 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 8 (Box 5)
    - July 14, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (25 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 9 (Box 5)
    - History Department, undated (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (25 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 10 (Box 5)
    - Biltmore House, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (25 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 11 (Box 5)
    - Columbia, 1954 (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (25 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 12 (Box 5)
    - Novick, May 1950 (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (25 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 13 (Box 5)
    - Unidentified (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (25 ft.) (Box 5)
  - Reel 14 (Box 5)
    - Unidentified (Box 5)
    - Reversal original, 8mm, si., col. (25 ft.) (Box 5)
Related Material
Duke University. President. William Preston Few records, 1910-1940.
University Archives, Duke University.
Duke University. President. Arthur H. Edens records, 1949-1960.
University Archives, Duke University.
Paul M. Gross papers.
University Archives, Duke University.